It's so good!
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
This is crazy.
We've arrived at the inferno!
Please wait!
Great view!
Amazing!
So delicious!
Fresh
Sweet
Kanaya-don!
Yes, I'm going strawberry picking today!
Thank you!
You love strawberries, don't you?
I love them!
Strawberries are my favorite fruit, so I was really looking forward to it!
Well, let's buy lots of strawberries today!
Yes! I'm looking forward to it!
Wow! I'm so excited!
When was the last time you went?
What? I've only been once before, for strawberry picking.
Oh, really?
Is that the closest?
I went there when I was in junior high school, once with my family.
Since then.
I've only been once.
It's my first time!
First time!
I'm going to pick strawberries here!
You're strong!
I got strawberries!
The shape of the strawberry, it's kind of cute with legs!
Beautiful shape!
And the color, too!
Shall we eat it then?
Yes! Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
Sweet!
Very tasty!
Delicious!
Oh, this looks so good.
Really?
It's amazing. It's like...
It comes out like a little girl's golf game.
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh.
Mmmm, yummy!
Ameer otome!
Oh, it's Otome!
Thank you so much. Wow!
Hmm?
Is there a difference?
It tastes totally different.
Ameer Tortoise, it's delicious!
Delicious!
All the way down to the bottom.
I got the red one!
I think the Ameaotome is sweeter because it contains a lot more water.
But they are both delicious!
I think this round one is better.
This one...
Which one do you want to take?
First of all, how about... first of all...
I don't know how to explain it.
I'm trying to take a picture without leaving any stems.
Why?
Aah! There it is!
I used both hands to get out.
It looks like he's trying not to leave any cookies!
Next time I want a parfait... a big strawberry parfait!
I'm looking forward to it!
Let's go inside the parfait!
I can see it now!
It's amazing!
Amazing!
It's so small! What is this?
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It goes so well with the dough cream!
It's so good!
Fresh!
Sweet!
What's in it?
Ice cream, maybe.
Milk ice cream.
That makes sense.
Cream and ice cream.
It's some kind of show cake.
It's got some kind of sponge in it.
Sponge?
Yes, sir.
Okay, I'm done with the cafe.
Let's do a report.
It's really, um, first of all...
It looks really big.
There are so many strawberries in it.
It's like a bouquet!
Like a bouquet of strawberries.
They're so beautiful.
And the cream goes really well with it.
It's like a shortcake inside.
It's like a shortcake with sponge and stuff.
And ice cream.
It was delicious.
And there were chocolate flakes under it.
And under that...
There was a joke in there.
It was a sandwich, right, guys?
Really, I ate a lot of strawberries today.
I'm gonna be a strawberry.
I don't get it.
The article is published by Highway Walker, so please check it out as well.
Please do.
Bye-bye.
We're at the Nokogiri Mountain Nippon-ji Temple today.
I think you can see it a little bit, but look at this back here.
It is said to be one of the largest Buddha statues in Japan.
It's huge!
I wonder if the camera can convey it.
Where are we going after this?
The top one, Jigoku-nozoki (peering into hell).
Jigoku-nozoki (peering into hell)
I've seen it in a picture.
I'd like to go there after this.
And, uh, what else?
And then, let's see...
Kaisendon (a bowl of rice topped with seafood)
I'm going to eat as much as I can.
I'm going to enjoy it as much as I can!
Yes, I'm heading to Hell's Peephole now.
I'm not running!
I'm going to climb up this high place to get there.
I think it's a bit of a walk
I'll do my best
Weak, weak, weak, weak
lamb
else
car arch
I'm a man's man, I'm a man's man
I'm done... no more...
Thank you for your hard work.
I think you can see it now.
That's where the hell is.
I see it!
Ready?
Yes, sir.
Hang in there!
You okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Yes, OK.
Yes, you have arrived at the Gate of Hell!
Congratulations!
Great view!
A great view and a nice breeze
It feels great!
It's a great view!
I'm so happy
Yamahiko?
Yamahiko.
I'm a fan.
That's right.
Yoo-hoo!
And it took us about 30 minutes to get here, right?
30 minutes? My legs were already wobbling.
But it was worth the effort to see this view.
It's a great view from here, but it's so much more powerful from the side.
I stayed here the whole time.
I'm going to leave you.
Do you want to do that?
We're going out to eat seafood together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We should get going.
I did it. I was looking forward to it.
Shall we go right away?
Let's go.
Kaisendon from here suddenly?
We're flying? Shall we go?
Don't do that.
It's a kaisendon.
So, we arrived at Yoko Cuisine Canoe to eat Kaisendon.
I am starving.
Let's go eat it right away.
Can we go from here at all?
I can go there, but I can't.
We can go there at all. I don't know what to do.
Please go.
Here it is.
Kanaya-don.
Yay!
Looks delicious.
It looks so delicious.
Marlin tuna, negitoro, shrimp, scallops, sea bream, salmon roe, etc.
And an egg omelet, too.
I'm so happy. Yay!
I'll take it. Thank you.
So, I got a bowl of kaisen-don.
I am already full.
But it was delicious.
Today, we started from Sanuki Katsurazan,
Katsurazan, and then to Jigoku-nozoki (peering into hell) at Katsurazan,
I had so much fun that I didn't know if I deserved such a reward.
I think we had a very nice trip.
It was fun.
It was so much fun.